Fuck it
Whispered round, low density
My fingers on my clit
and I am gone
And I am gone
My hand between my thighs
sliding down
I come alone
I come loud I come for me
Come for me
Break down
vocal and zipper pole
only
I lock the door, I lie back on the sheet,
my hands sliding over my hip bone into the
heat.
Finding the wetness between my legs
circling.
I press my fingers against myself and arch
my back.
My left hand on my breast, my nipple
heart.
My right hand, two fingers deep
inside me.
My thumb on my clip, shaking.
I am close.
I know how to make myself calm.
Make myself calm.
Three voice round voices entering one bar
apart.
Stripping back to one.
Failure first, failure first.
AI safety research.
Safety research
failure first
dot a
i